A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18 FA290
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1; 171.6 Cubic Feet; 390 boxes, 532 microfilm reels
  - University of Pennsylvania (Henry Phipps Institute) - Resistance and Susceptibility to Experimental Tuberculosis Study - Financial Data, 1941-1950 (Box 268, Folder 2565)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1937-1941 (Box 269, Folder 2566)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1937-1941 (Box 269, Folder 2567)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1937-1941 (Box 269, Folder 2568)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1937-1941 (Box 269, Folder 2569)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1937-1941 (Box 269, Folder 2570)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1937-1941 (Box 269, Folder 2571)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1937-1941 (Box 269, Folder 2572)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1937-1941 (Box 269, Folder 2573)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1942-1948 (Box 270, Folder 2574)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1942-1948 (Box 270, Folder 2575)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1942-1948 (Box 270, Folder 2576)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1942-1948 (Box 270, Folder 2577)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study, 1942-1948 (Box 270, Folder 2578)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Financial Data, 1937-1945 (Box 270, Folder 2579)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Financial Data, 1937-1945 (Box 270, Folder 2580)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Financial Data, 1937-1945 (Box 270, Folder 2581)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Progress Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 271, Folder 2582)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Progress Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 271, Folder 2583)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Progress Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 271, Folder 2584)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Progress Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 271, Folder 2585)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Progress Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 271, Folder 2586)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Progress Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 271, Folder 2587)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Prevention and Control of Air-borne Infections Study - Progress Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 271, Folder 2588)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Professional Training of Teachers, May 1, 1922 (Box 271, Folder 2589)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Psychiatric Fellowships, 1925-1929 (Box 271, Folder 2590)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Psychiatric Fellowships, 1925-1929 (Box 271, Folder 2591)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Research Laboratories in Connection with the New Gynecological-Obstetrical Hospital, 1938-1947 (Box 271, Folder 2592)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1966-1974 (Box 272, Folder 2593)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1966-1974 (Box 272, Folder 2594)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1966-1974 (Box 272, Folder 2595)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1966-1974 (Box 272, Folder 2596)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1966-1974 (Box 272, Folder 2597)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1966-1974 (Box 272, Folder 2598)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1966-1974 (Box 272, Folder 2599)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1966-1974 (Box 272, Folder 2600)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1966-1974 (Box 272, Folder 2601)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1974-1976 (Box 273, Folder 2602)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1974-1976 (Box 273, Folder 2603)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1974-1976 (Box 273, Folder 2604)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine, 1974-1976 (Box 273, Folder 2605)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Center for the Study of Sex Education in Medicine - Eastern Regional Workshop for Medical Education, 1969-1974 (Box 273, Folder 2606)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Chemical Study of Virus Formation (MR), 1948-1955 (Box 273, Folder 2607)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Chemical Study of Virus Formation (MR), 1948-1955 (Box 273, Folder 2608)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Chemical Study of Virus Formation (MR), 1948-1955 (Box 273, Folder 2609)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Chemical Study of Virus Formation (MR), 1948-1955 (Box 273, Folder 2610)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Chemical Study of Virus Formation (MR), 1948-1955 (Box 273, Folder 2611)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Chemical Study of Virus Formation (MR), 1956-1966 (Box 274, Folder 2612)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Chemical Study of Virus Formation (MR), 1956-1966 (Box 274, Folder 2613)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Chemical Study of Virus Formation (MR), 1956-1966 (Box 274, Folder 2614)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Chemical Study of Virus Formation (Financial Data) (MR), 1949-1951 (Box 274, Folder 2615)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Mechanism of Antibody Formation Study, 1948-1955 (Box 274, Folder 2616)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Mechanism of Antibody Formation Study, 1948-1955 (Box 274, Folder 2617)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia - Mechanism of Antibody Formation Study, 1948-1955 (Box 274, Folder 2618)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Department of Bacteriology - Streptococcus Study, 1937-1939 (Box 274, Folder 2619)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Department of Bacteriology - Streptococcus Study, 1937-1939 (Box 274, Folder 2620)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Department of Bacteriology - Streptococcus Study, 1940-1943 (Box 275, Folder 2621)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Department of Bacteriology - Streptococcus Study (Financial Data), 1938-1941 (Box 275, Folder 2622)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine (ME&CH), 1969-1973 (Box 275, Folder 2623)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine (ME&CH), 1969-1973 (Box 275, Folder 2624)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine - Consortium of West Philadelphia Mental Health (ME&CH), May 5-9, 1969 (Box 275, Folder 2625)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine - Reports (ME&CH), 1971 and 1975 (Box 275, Folder 2626)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine - Reports (ME&CH), 1971 and 1975 (Box 275, Folder 2627)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine - Reports (ME&CH), 1971 and 1975 (Box 275, Folder 2628)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine - Reports (ME&CH), 1971 and 1975 (Box 275, Folder 2629)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine - Reports (ME&CH), 1974-1975 (Box 276, Folder 2630)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine - Reports (ME&CH), 1974-1975 (Box 276, Folder 2631)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Development of New Programs in Community Medicine - Reports (ME&CH), 1974-1975 (Box 276, Folder 2632)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Family Advisor Program, 1951-1958 (Box 276, Folder 2633)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Family Advisor Program, 1951-1958 (Box 276, Folder 2634)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Family Advisor Program, 1951-1958 (Box 276, Folder 2635)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Family Advisor Program, 1951-1958 (Box 276, Folder 2636)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - National Conference on Sex Education in Medicine, 1973-1975 (Box 276, Folder 2637)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - New Techniques of Respiratory Physiology Study, 1947-1951 (Box 277, Folder 2638)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - New Techniques of Respiratory Physiology Study - Financial Data, 1948-1953 (Box 277, Folder 2639)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Normals Study, 1929-1934 (Box 277, Folder 2640)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Normals Study, 1929-1934 (Box 277, Folder 2641)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Normals Study, 1929-1934 (Box 277, Folder 2642)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney, 1931-1935 (Box 277, Folder 2643)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney, 1931-1935 (Box 277, Folder 2644)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney, 1931-1935 (Box 277, Folder 2645)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney, 1936-1966 (Box 278, Folder 2646)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney, 1936-1966 (Box 278, Folder 2647)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney, 1936-1966 (Box 278, Folder 2648)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney - Financial Data, 1931-1942 (Box 278, Folder 2649)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney - Financial Data, 1931-1942 (Box 278, Folder 2650)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney - Financial Data, 1931-1942 (Box 278, Folder 2651)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney - Financial Data, 1931-1942 (Box 278, Folder 2652)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney - Financial Data, 1931-1942 (Box 278, Folder 2653)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Research on the Function of the Kidney - Financial Data, 1931-1942 (Box 278, Folder 2654)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Support for Key Faculty in the Department of Community Medicine (ME&CH), 1971-1977 (Box 279, Folder 2655)
  - University of Pennsylvania (School of Medicine) - Support for Key Faculty in the Department of Community Medicine (ME&CH), 1971-1977 (Box 279, Folder 2656)
  - College of Physicians of Pennsylvania - Development of the College's Role as a Scholarly Library Center in Medicine (ME&CH), 1967-1974 (Box 279, Folder 2657)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1956-1960 (Box 279, Folder 2658)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1956-1960 (Box 279, Folder 2659)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1956-1960 (Box 279, Folder 2660)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1956-1960 (Box 279, Folder 2661)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1956-1960 (Box 279, Folder 2662)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1956-1960 (Box 279, Folder 2663)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1961-1963 (Box 280, Folder 2664)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1961-1963 (Box 280, Folder 2665)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1961-1963 (Box 280, Folder 2666)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Development of Objective Measures of Medical Ability and Proficiency (ME&CH), 1961-1963 (Box 280, Folder 2667)
  - University of Pittsburgh (School of Medicine) - Department of Orthopedic Surgery - Programmed Instruction about the Musculo-skeletal System (ME&CH), 1964-1966 (Box 280, Folder 2668)
  - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - General Support, 1946-1948 (Box 280, Folder 2669)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Consulting Services and RElated Costs of Increasing Public Education Through Various New Outlets Statewide, About the Record and Benefits of Legal Abortion Services in New York State, 1979-1980 (Box 280, Folder 2670)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Creation of an International Training Center for Physicians and Allied Health Workers in the Field of Family Planning, 1972-1977 (Box 280, Folder 2671)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Creation of an International Training Center for Physicians and Allied Health Workers in the Field of Family Planning, 1972-1977 (Box 280, Folder 2672)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Experiment in Sex Education, Counseling, and Related Medical Services for Urban Ghetto Youth, 1967-1968 (Box 280, Folder 2673)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Experiment in Sex Education, Counseling and Related Medical Services for Urban Ghetto Youth, 1968-1978 (Box 281, Folder 2674)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Experiment in Sex Education, Counseling and Related Medical Services for Urban Ghetto Youth, 1968-1978 (Box 281, Folder 2675)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Experiment in Sex Education, Counseling and Related Medical Services for Urban Ghetto Youth, 1968-1978 (Box 281, Folder 2676)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Experiment in Sex Education, Counseling and Related Medical Services for Urban Ghetto Youth, 1968-1978 (Box 281, Folder 2677)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Experiment in Sex Education, Counseling and Related Medical Services for Urban Ghetto Youth, 1968-1978 (Box 281, Folder 2678)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Experiment in Sex Education, Counseling and Related Medical Services for Urban Ghetto Youth, 1968-1978 (Box 281, Folder 2679)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Family Planning Crisis Fund Reorganization of New York City Family Planning Services Threatened by City Budget Cuts, 1976-1979 (Box 281, Folder 2680)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - Margaret Sanger Center - International Student Program, 1977-1979 (Box 281, Folder 2681)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), June-August, 1968 (Box 281, Folder 2682)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2683)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2684)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2685)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2686)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2687)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2688)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2689)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2690)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2691)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development (ME&CH), 1968-1975 (Box 282, Folder 2692)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development/Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1973-1981 (Box 283, Folder 2693)
    See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, Guttmacher Institute, Boxes 112-113, Folders 1034-1043.
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development/Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1973-1981 (Box 283, Folder 2694)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development/Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1973-1981 (Box 283, Folder 2695)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development/Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1973-1981 (Box 283, Folder 2696)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development/Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1973-1981 (Box 283, Folder 2697)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development/Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1973-1981 (Box 283, Folder 2698)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development/Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1973-1981 (Box 283, Folder 2699)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Center for Family Planning Program Development/Alan Guttmacher Institute, 1973-1981 (Box 283, Folder 2700)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Expansion of the Work of the International Planned Parenthood Federation Program (ME&CH), June-September, 1965 (Box 283, Folder 2701)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Expansion of the Work of the International Planned Parenthood Federation Program (ME&CH), 1965-1968 (Box 284, Folder 2702)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Expansion of the Work of the International Planned Parenthood Federation Program (ME&CH), 1965-1968 (Box 284, Folder 2703)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Expansion of the Work of the International Planned Parenthood Federation Program (ME&CH), 1965-1968 (Box 284, Folder 2704)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Expansion of the Work of the International Planned Parenthood Federation Program (ME&CH), 1965-1968 (Box 284, Folder 2705)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Film for Medical Students and Physicians on Conceptions Control (ME&CH), 1959-1974 (Box 284, Folder 2706)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Film for Medical Students and Physicians on Conceptions Control (ME&CH), 1959-1974 (Box 284, Folder 2707)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Film for Medical Students and Physicians on Conceptions Control (ME&CH), 1959-1974 (Box 284, Folder 2708)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Film for Medical Students and Physicians on Conceptions Control (ME&CH), 1959-1974 (Box 284, Folder 2709)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Film for Medical Students and Physicians on Conceptions Control (ME&CH), 1959-1974 (Box 284, Folder 2710)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Film for Medical Students and Physicians on Conceptions Control (ME&CH), 1959-1974 (Box 284, Folder 2711)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Victor-Bostrom Fund to Assist the Work of the International Planned Parenthood Federation (ME&CH), 1968-1974 (Box 285, Folder 2712)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Victor-Bostrom Fund to Assist the Work of the International Planned Parenthood Federation (ME&CH), 1968-1974 (Box 285, Folder 2713)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population - Victor-Bostrom Fund to Assist the Work of the International Planned Parenthood Federation (ME&CH), 1968-1974 (Box 285, Folder 2714)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Biological and Medical Fellowships (F&AHF), 1961-1971 (Box 285, Folder 2715)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Biological and Medical Fellowships (F&AHF), 1961-1971 (Box 285, Folder 2716)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Implementation of Family Planning in Large Delivery Hospitals (ME&CH), 1965-1969 (Box 285, Folder 2717)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Implementation of Family Planning in Large Delivery Hospitals (ME&CH), 1965-1969 (Box 285, Folder 2718)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Implementation of Family Planning in Large Delivery Hospitals (ME&CH), 1965-1969 (Box 285, Folder 2719)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Implementation of Family Planning in Large Delivery Hospitals (ME&CH), 1965-1969 (Box 285, Folder 2720)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Implementation of Family Planning in Large Delivery Hospitals (ME&CH), 1965-1969 (Box 285, Folder 2721)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Pre-packaged Lecture Series on Population for Use in Medical and Nursing Schools in the Developing World, 1973-1979 (Box 286, Folder 2722)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Pre-packaged Lecture Series on Population for Use in Medical and Nursing Schools in the Developing World, 1973-1979 (Box 286, Folder 2723)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Research, Education and Program Development Related to International Population Growth, 1979-1982 (Box 286, Folder 2724)
  - Population Council, Inc. - Research, Education and Program Development Related to International Population Growth, 1979-1982 (Box 286, Folder 2725)
  - Population Council, Inc./International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction, Columbia University - Planning Program to Integrate Family Planning into Rural Maternal-Care Services (ME&CH), 1968-1974 (Box 286, Folder 2726)